a message from your Governor price
Daniel my fellow Texans I appeal to you
to join hands in a Statewide campaign
for safety and against death and
destruction on our streets and highways
last year over 2600 people were killed
and over 300,000 injured in traffic
accidents in Texas this is worse than
all of the combined destruction of our
floods tornadoes and other disasters
your state officials believe that there
is something we can do to stop this
destruction but we need your help we ask
that all Tex's citizens drive carefully
obey the laws and support the law
enforcement officers who are cracking
down on those who violate the laws let's
begin on July the 4th last year 12 were
killed over 300 injured on July 4th
let's make it different this year by
celebrating the fourth with safety in
Texas